We're trying to collect
as much information as we can
to get a clear picture on what's going on
and figure out where to start. okay?
-Okay.
-Um… Starting yesterday.
-did you go to the football game?
-No. I was at work.
What did you do after you got off shift?
I went home
and met up with my friends.
and then we went to the Corner Club.
Eventually. I came back home.
-Have roommates? They there?
-Mm-hm. Yeah.
What time did you guys
make it home from the bar?
1:30ish.
-You were with him all night?
-Mm-hmm.
You're not in trouble.
I just gotta ask questions.
Talk me through the rest of your evening.
You guys hang out?
I came back home.
Pretty much just went to bed.
You had missed calls from
Kaylee. Remember what time. by chance?
Yeah. they were.
like. between 2:40 and 3:00.
The last one was. like. 2:57.
Kaylee has called me and stuff.
like. if she's walking home.
and she thinks someone. like.
is watching or following her.
she'll call me and just…
-Just to have someone on the phone.
-Yeah. yeah.
Did she ever mention that
she thought someone was following her.
or was it more just getting creeped out?
Yeah. just got creeped out.
Um. ever had any roommates
complain about anyone stalking them?
Mm-mm.
Once though. Kaylee said
when everyone was. like. gone
and it was only Kaylee
and she was taking Murphy out.
and she said she swears
she saw someone staring at her
while she was taking the dog out to pee.
She could see. like.
a man's silhouette staring at her.
-Know how long ago that was?
-Maybe like a month.
About a week ago. our door is broken
but me. Maddie and Bethany got home
and the door was wide open.
Did you ever. uh.
find the back slider open or anything?
-Is that usually locked?
-We're pretty good at locking it.
I don't think we locked it last night.
There's a lot of people coming in
and out of their house all the time
just because they're well-liked people.
This may seem like a weird question.
but who would do something like this?
I couldn't even imagine.
We're just trying
to put the pieces of the puzzle together.
um. just with everything that's going on.
We're gonna go back and try
to get a little bit of the timeline. okay?
Yeah.
When was the last time
that you were over at…?
The last time before today was yesterday.
Okay. What were you doing there yesterday?
We were pre-gaming
the football game for the Vandals.
Gotcha.
We left their house
and went to a different apartment
at roughly. like. 2:30.
We were just hanging out at our house.
Ethan was at formal
because he went with his sister
because she didn't have a date.
And then he came over
and then we all walked over together.
And the last time you saw
Xana and Ethan was at the Sigma Chi house?
-Mm.
-Okay.
You. Ethan. Xana…
Was there another person with you?
-Or just three of you that walked?
-Uh. Maddie walked over with us.
Were you guys all together.
or just kind of mingling
throughout the house?
We were all pretty much together
and then Maddie left
to go to the club with Kaylee.
What happened next?
I did run into Kaylee at the Corner Club.
said hi to her. talked to her
for probably a minute or so.
I don't even really remember what our…
We had a 30-second conversation.
Okay.
Did it seem normal? Did it seem off?
-Yeah. everything seemed normal.
-Okay.
So. what…
Let's go a little bit more.
They went to Grub Truck after the club.
Okay.
-Hello!
-Hi.
Welcome back.
Thanks. I think I would like the. um…
Well. it's all over the news.
The rumor out there is
somebody died here from fentanyl.
And then somebody else said
somebody might have got stabbed.
I said.
"Well. I can't confirm any of that."
So… But the rumors are out there.
Oh. yeah.
-Are you guys out of here?
-Yeah.
-I'll mark you off.
-All right.
-You have a camera.
-Yes.
-Have other cameras?
-Just that one.
-How big? Mind if I see?
-The road. it cuts out…
Just the driveway.
-Here's the SD card.
-I appreciate that.
-Of course.
-Thank you.
-Hey there.
-Hi.
I stopped you going a little fast.
Do you realize this is. uh. 35?
-Oh. it's 35?
-It is. yeah. So you were going--
-About 41?
-Yeah. 43 was what the radar said.
-Can I get a phone number?
-Yeah. why?
Uh. we need to put it on the citation
as it goes to the court.
-Hello. How y'all doing today?
-How you doing?
Good. good.
So you was right up on that van. man.
You're coming
from Washington State University?
-Yeah.
-And you're going where?
-We're gonna be going to Pennsylvania.
-Okay.